Planned Parenthood Federation of America Records (PPFA II): SERIES V. Affiliates, 1930-80 (Part 1)
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES V. AFFILIATES (PART 1)
  - Alabama
    - Mobile, PP Association, 1965-1967 (Box 141, Folder 39)
    - Selma, PP League of Dallas County, Correspondence, 1965 (Box 141, Folder 40)
    - Tuscaloosa
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1961-1972 (Box 141, Folder 41)
      - Affiliation, PP Association, Correspondence from 1971
        - 1971-1974 (Box 141, Folder 42)
        - 1975-1977 (Box 141)
      - PP Association of Tuscaloosa County from 1970
        - 1970-1974 (Box 141, Folder 43)
        - 1975-1977 (Box 141)
    - Field Trips, General, 1961 (Box 141, Folder 44)
    - Southeast Region, Reports, Field Trips, 1964-1969 (Box 141, Folder 45)
  - Alaska
    - Contacts, 1965-1972 (Box 141, Folder 46)
    - Legal, circa 1968 (Box 141, Folder 47)
    - General from 1962
      - 1968-1974 (Box 141, Folder 48)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 141)
    - Anchorage
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1968
        - 1968-1974 (Box 141, Folder 49)
        - 1977-1978 (Box 141)
      - Affiliation, Correspondence from 1967
        - 1967-1974 (Box 141, Folder 50)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 141)
      - Anchorage PP League, 1977-1979 (Box 141, Folder 51)
      - Anchorage PP League from 1966
        - 1966-1974 (Box 141, Folder 52)
        - 1975 (Box 141)
      - Anchorage PP League, Reports, Members from 1966
        - 1966-1973 (Box 141, Folder 53)
        - 1976-1977 (Box 141)
      - Field Visit, 1973 (Box 141, Folder 54)
    - Juneau-Douglas, Planned Parenthood of Juneau-Douglas, 1970-1971 (Box 141, Folder 55)
    - Fairbanks, Northern Alaska PP, Inc., 1966-1972 (Box 141, Folder 56)
    - Western Region, Reports, Field Trips, 1966-1972 (Box 141, Folder 57)
  - Arizona, Anti-Poverty Program, 1964-1972 (Box 142, Folder 1)
  - Arkansas, Contacts from 1960
    - 1964-1971 (Box 142, Folder 2)
    - 1977-1980 (Box 142)
  - Arizona
    - Contacts from 1960
      - 1964-1972 (Box 142, Folder 3)
      - 1977 (Box 142)
    - Hospitals, 1963 (Box 142, Folder 4)
    - Legal, (Paul, Eve), 1979 (Box 142, Folder 5)
    - Legal, 1941-1972 (Box 142, Folder 6)
    - Migrant, 1964-1968 (Box 142, Folder 7)
    - Migrant, Field Trips, 1959-1962 (Box 142, Folder 8)
    - Public Health, 1964-1974 (Box 142, Folder 9)
    - Public Welfare, 1964-1968 (Box 142, Folder 10)
    - Western Region, Reports, Field Trips, 1964-1971 (Box 142, Folder 11)
    - Schools, General, 1963-1972 (Box 142, Folder 12)
    - Phoenix
      - Field Trips, 1954-1964 (Box 142, Folder 13)
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1960
        - 1957-1974 (Box 142, Folder 14)
        - 1976-1979 (Box 142)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1957
        - 1959-1974 (Box 142, Folder 15)
        - 1976-1980 (Box 142)
      - PP Association, 1975-1979 (Box 142, Folder 16)
      - PP Association, 1970-1974 (Box 142, Folder 17)
      - PP Association, 1964-1969 (Box 142, Folder 18)
      - PP Association, Chapters, Prescott-Yavapai from 1972
        - 1972-1974 (Box 142, Folder 19)
        - 1975 (Box 142)
      - PP Association, Reports, Clinics from 1962 (empty) (Box 142, Folder 20)
      - PP Association, Reports, General, 1964-1969 (Box 142, Folder 21)
      - PP Association, Reports, Members from 1962
        - 1964-1972 (Box 142, Folder 22)
        - 1976 (Box 142)
      - PP Association, Publicity, 1964-1969 (Box 142, Folder 23)
    - Tucson
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1957
        - 1957-1973 (Box 142, Folder 24)
        - 1976-1979 (Box 142)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1959
        - 1959-1973 (Box 142, Folder 25)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 142)
      - PP of Southern Arizona, Legal (Paul), 1978 (Box 142, Folder 26)
      - PP Center 1970
        - 1970-1974 (Box 142, Folder 27)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 142)
      - PP Clinic, 1964-1969 (Box 142, Folder 28)
      - Field Trips, 1954-1963 (Box 142, Folder 29)
      - PP Clinic, Reports, General, 1968-1969 (Box 142, Folder 30)
      - PP Clinic, Reports, Members, 1964-1972 (Box 142, Folder 31)
      - PP Clinic, Reports, Clinics, 1965-1970 (Box 142, Folder 32)
      - PP Clinic, Publicity, 1965-1969 (Box 142, Folder 33)
    - Yuma, Yuma Family Planning, 1965-1969 (Box 142, Folder 34)
  - Arkansas
    - Perryville, Field Trips, 1956 (Box 142, Folder 35)
    - Anti-Poverty, 1965-1970 (Box 142, Folder 36)
    - Hospitals, 1963-1967 (Box 142, Folder 37)
    - Legal, 1943 (Box 142, Folder 38)
    - Migrants, 1969 (Box 142, Folder 39)
    - Projects, 1970 (Box 142, Folder 40)
    - Public Health, 1965-1973 (Box 142, Folder 41)
    - Public Welfare, 1966-1970 (Box 142, Folder 42)
    - Schools, General, 1968-1974 (Box 142, Folder 43)
    - Pine Bluff, Agricultural, Mechanical and Normal College, 1958-1965 (Box 142, Folder 44)
    - University of, 1961-1970 (Box 142, Folder 45)
    - Little Rock
      - Affiliation, PP Association, 1959-1955 (Box 142, Folder 46)
      - Field Trips, 1954 (Box 142, Folder 47)
      - PP Association, 1963-1971 (Box 142, Folder 48)
  - California
    - Anti-Poverty Program, 1964-1972 (Box 142, Folder 49)
    - Legal Abortion, "Ballard v. Anderson," 1970-1971 (Box 142, Folder 50)
    - California Interagency Council on Family Planning, General, 1969-1970 (Box 142, Folder 51)
    - California Interagency Council on Family Planning, Correspondence, 1967-1974 (Box 142, Folder 52)
    - Chad, Combined Health Agencies Drive, 1975-1977 (Box 142, Folder 53)
    - Contacts from 1969
      - 1969-1974 (Box 142, Folder 54)
      - 1975-1977 (Box 142)
    - Contacts, 1964-1968 (Box 142, Folder 55)
    - Department HEW, Region IX, Family Planning Services from 1971
      - 1971-1974 (Box 142, Folder 56)
      - 1975-1977 (Box 142)
    - Hospitals from 1956
      - 1963-1974 (Box 142, Folder 57)
      - 1976 (Box 142)
    - Legal
      - from 1959
        - 1953-1974 (Box 142, Folder 58)
        - 1979 (Box 142)
      - Pasadena, Situation, 1961: "Christie v. Griggs," 1961-1966 (Box 142, Folder 59)
      - Belous Case, Abortion, 1969 (Box 142, Folder 60)
      - Los Angeles, Situation, 1961-1962 (Box 142, Folder 61)
    - Medical Resolutions, 1962-1968 (Box 142, Folder 62)
    - Midcoast Comprehensive Planning Association, 1972 (Box 142, Folder 63)
    - Migrant, 1959-1974 (Box 142, Folder 64)
    - PERCC (Public Education Research Committee of California) from 1971
      - 1970-1974 (Box 142, Folder 65)
      - 1975 (Box 142)
    - Projects, 1969 (Box 142, Folder 66)
    - Public Health
      - from 1969
        - 1969-1974 (Box 142, Folder 67)
        - 1975-1977 (Box 142)
      - Correspondence, 1961-1968 (Box 142, Folder 68)
      - Field Trips, 1963-1965 (Box 142, Folder 69)
      - Publications, Reports, Miscellaneous, 1963-1965 (Box 142, Folder 70)
    - Public Welfare
      - Assembly Committee on Social Welfare, Los Angeles, 9/13/1964-1965 (Box 142, Folder 71)
      - Correspondence, 1963-1972 (Box 143, Folder 1)
      - Carl Reiterman, 1962-1967 (Box 143, Folder 2)
    - Sales and Use Tax Regulations, Legal Department, 1979 (Box 143, Folder 3)
    - United Fund, 1968-1969 (Box 143, Folder 4)
    - U.S. Equal Employment Opportunity Commission, 1979 (Box 143, Folder 5)
    - Dr. Guttmacher's Trip 1-2/66, 1965-1966 (Box 143, Folder 6)
    - Dr. Guttmacher's Trip, 4/65, 1963-1965 (Box 143, Folder 7)
    - General, Schools, Correspondence from 1955
      - 1962-1974 (Box 143, Folder 8)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 143)
    - Pasadena, Schools, California Institute of Technology, Dr. Harrison Brown, 1956-1962 (Box 143, Folder 9)
    - Cal. Tech., "Brave New World," Dr. Harrison S. Brown, 1956 (Box 143, Folder 10)
    - Stanford University, Correspondence, General from 1953
      - 1953-1973 (Box 143, Folder 11)
      - 1975 (Box 143)
    - Stanford University, Weldon Gibson's Manuscript on World Population, 1962-1963 (Box 143, Folder 12)
    - University of California, Correspondence, General, 1963-1973 (Box 143, Folder 13)
    - University of California, Family Planning Seminar, 1961-1967 (Box 143, Folder 14)
    - University of San Francisco, A Study on Catholic Marriage in the U.S., 1968 (Box 143, Folder 15)
    - Affiliation, PP Affiliates of California, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1974
      - 1974 (Box 143, Folder 16)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 143)
    - Bakersfield
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1963-1973 (Box 143, Folder 17)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence, 1963-1973 (Box 143, Folder 18)
    - PP Affiliates of California, PPAC: Legal, 1978-1979 (Box 143, Folder 19)
    - Planned Parenthood Affiliates of California (formerly Council of California PP Affiliates), PPAC from 1973
      - 1973-1974 (Box 143, Folder 20)
      - 1975-1979 (Box 143)
    - Bakersfield
      - PP Association of Kern County from 1968
        - 1968-1973 (Box 143, Folder 21)
        - 1978 (Box 143)
      - PP Committee, 1963-1967 (Box 143, Folder 22)
      - Field Trips, 1963-1964 (Box 143, Folder 23)
      - PP Bakersfield, Reports, Clinics, 1965 (Box 143, Folder 24)
      - PP Bakersfield, Reports, General, 1965-1969 (Box 143, Folder 25)
      - PP Bakersfield, Reports, Members, 1963-1972 (Box 143, Folder 26)
      - PP Bakersfield, Publicity, 1964-1967 (Box 143, Folder 27)
    - Burlingame, Field Trips, 1960-1963 (Box 143, Folder 28)
    - Claremont, PP Pomona Valley, 1965-1966 (Box 143, Folder 29)
    - Davis, Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, Documents from 1971
      - 1971-1973 (Box 143, Folder 30)
      - 1975-1979 (Box 143)
      - Affiliation, PP Association of Yolo County (formerly in Woodland), Correspondence from 1971
        - 1971-1974 (Box 143, Folder 31)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 143)
      - PP Association of Yolo County (formerly in Woodland), Legal (Paul, Eve), 1979 (Box 143, Folder 32)
      - PP Association of Yolo County (formerly in Woodland) from 1971
        - 1971-1973 (Box 143, Folder 33)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 143)
      - PP Yolo County, Field Visit Reports, 1977 (Box 143, Folder 34)
      - PP Yolo County (formerly in Woodland), Reports, Members from 1974
        - 1974 (Box 143, Folder 35)
        - 1976-1978 (Box 143)
    - Eureka
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1975-1980 (Box 143, Folder 36)
      - Affiliation, PP of Humboldt County, 1977-1980 (Box 143, Folder 37)
      - PP Humboldt County, 1975-1979 (Box 143, Folder 38)
    - Fresno, Field Trips, 1954 (Box 143, Folder 39)
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1971
        - 1971-1973 (Box 143, Folder 40)
        - 1977-1980 (Box 143)
      - Affiliation, PP Fresno, Correspondence from 1971
        - 1971-1974 (Box 143, Folder 41)
        - 1976-1977 (Box 143)
      - PP of Fresno from 1971
        - 1971-1974 (Box 143, Folder 42)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 143)
      - Reports, Members from 1971
        - 1971-1972 (Box 143, Folder 43)
        - 1976-1977 (Box 143)
    - Huntington Park
      - Affiliation, PP Committee, 1953-1955 (Box 143, Folder 44)
      - PP Committee, 1953-1954 (Box 143, Folder 45)
      - Field Trips, 1951-1953 (Box 143, Folder 46)
    - Merced, PP, 1964-1966 (Box 143, Folder 47)
    - Napa City, PP of Napa City, 1965-1967 (Box 143, Folder 48)
    - Oakland
      - Affiliation, PP League, Correspondence, 1952-1969 (Box 143, Folder 49)
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws,1949-1969 (Box 143, Folder 50)
      - PP Alameda County, Merger, 1969 (Box 143, Folder 51)
      - PP League, 1967-1969 (Box 143, Folder 52)
      - PP League, 1965-1966 (Box 143, Folder 53)
      - Field Trips from 1951, 1951-1960 (Box 143, Folder 54)
      - PP League, Reports, Clinics, 1963 (Box 143, Folder 55)
      - PP League, Reports, General, 1963-1970 (Box 143, Folder 56)
      - PP League, Reports, Members, 1963-1969 (Box 143, Folder 57)
      - PP League, Publicity, 1964-1969 (Box 143, Folder 58)
    - Santa Ana
      - Orange, Reports, General, 1966-1970 (Box 143, Folder 59)
      - Orange, Reports, Members, 1965-1972 (Box 143, Folder 60)
      - Orange, Publicity, 1965 (Box 143, Folder 61)
    - Pacific Grove
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, Monterey County, 1970-1974 (Box 144, Folder 1)
      - Affiliation, Monterey County, Correspondence from 1970
        - 1970-1974 (Box 144, Folder 2)
        - 1976-1978 (Box 144)
      - PP of Monterey County from 1970
        - 1970-1974 (Box 144, Folder 3)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 144)
    - Monterey PP, Reports, Members from 1970
      - 1970-1972 (Box 144, Folder 4)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 144)
    - Pasadena
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1950
        - 1950-1974 (Box 144, Folder 5)
        - 1978 (Box 144)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1950
        - 1950-1973 (Box 144, Folder 6)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 144)
      - Pasadena PP Committee, Inc. from 1970
        - 1970-1974 (Box 144, Folder 7)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 144)
      - PP Committee, 1965-1969 (Box 144, Folder 8)
      - PP Committee, 1964 (Box 144, Folder 9)
      - PP Committee, Reports, Clinics, 1960-1963 (Box 144, Folder 10)
      - PP Committee, Reports, General, 1960-1970 (Box 144, Folder 11)
      - PP Committee, Reports, Members from 1964
        - 1963-1973 (Box 144, Folder 12)
        - 1976-1978 (Box 144)
      - PP Committee, Publicity, 1959-1967 (Box 144, Folder 13)
      - Field Trips, 1951-1963 (Box 144, Folder 14)
    - Peninsula PP, Program, 1959-1963 (Box 144, Folder 15)
    - Peninsula, Field Trips, 1960 (Box 144, Folder 16)
    - Richmond
      - Affiliation, PP League, 1949-1954 (Box 144, Folder 17)
      - PP of Contra Costa, 1950-1962 (Box 144, Folder 18)
      - Field Trips, 1950-1953 (Box 144, Folder 19)
    - Riverside, Family Service Association of Riverside, 1965-1966 (Box 144, Folder 20)
    - Sacramento
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1964
        - 1964-1974 (Box 144, Folder 21)
        - 1977-1980 (Box 144)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1964
        - 1964-1974 (Box 144, Folder 22)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 144)
      - PP Association of Sacramento County from 1969
        - 1969-1974 (Box 144, Folder 23)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 144)
      - PP Committee from 1963
        - 1963-1974 (Box 144, Folder 24)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 144)
      - PP Association of Sacramento Workshop 3/27/1971 (Box 144, Folder 25)
      - Reports, General, 1964-1968 (Box 144, Folder 26)
      - Report, Members from 1964
        - 1964-1972 (Box 144, Folder 27)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 144)
      - Publicity, 1964-1972 (Box 144, Folder 28)
      - Field Trips, 1963-1964 (Box 144, Folder 29)
    - San Bernardino
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1966
        - 1968-1970 (Box 144, Folder 30)
        - 1980 (Box 144)
      - Affiliation, PP Council, Correspondence from 1966
        - 1966-1972 (Box 144, Folder 31)
        - 1977 (Box 144)
      - PP Council of San Bernardino County, 1965-1973 (Box 144, Folder 32)
      - PP Council, Reports, General, 1966-1969 (Box 144, Folder 33)
      - PP Council, Reports, Members from 1966
        - 1966-1970 (Box 144, Folder 34)
        - 1975 (Box 144)
      - Affiliation, PP Clinic, 1950 (Box 144, Folder 35)
      - PP Clinic, 1937 to 1956 (Box 144, Folder 36)
    - San Diego
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1969
        - 1969-1973 (Box 144, Folder 37)
        - 1978 (Box 144)
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1964-1967 (Box 144, Folder 38)
      - Affiliation, PP Association of San Diego County from 1969
        - 1969-1974 (Box 144, Folder 39)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 144)
      - Affiliation, PP Association of San Diego, 1960-1968 (Box 144, Folder 40)
      - PP Association of San Diego, Legal (Paul, Eve), 1978-1979 (Box 144, Folder 41)
      - PP of San Diego County, 1975-1979 (Box 144, Folder 42)
      - PP Association of San Diego County, 1969-1974 (Box 144, Folder 43)
      - PP Chapter, 1964-1968 (Box 144, Folder 44)
      - San Diego County, Statistics, circa 1970-1971 (Box 144, Folder 45)
      - Reports, Clinics, 1963-1969 (Box 144, Folder 46)
      - Reports, General, 1964-1969 (Box 144, Folder 47)
      - PP, Report, Members from 1963
        - 1963-1973 (Box 144, Folder 48)
        - 1977-1978 (Box 144)
      - Publicity, 1963-1973 (Box 144, Folder 49)
      - Dr. A.F.G.'s Trip, 5/1963 (Box 144, Folder 50)
      - Field Trips, 1959-1965 (Box 144, Folder 51)
    - San Bernardino, Field Trips, 1950-1953 (Box 144, Folder 52)
    - San Francisco
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, PP Alameda/ San Francisco, 1976-1979 (Box 144, Folder 53)
      - Affiliation, PP Alameda/San Francisco, Correspondence, 1976-1980 (Box 144, Folder 54)
      - PP Alameda/San Francisco, Documentation and Correspondence with Regional Office, 1978 (Box 144, Folder 55)
    - Oakland
      - Affiliation, PP Alameda/San Francisco, Correspondence, 1970-1974 (Box 144, Folder 56)
      - Affiliation, PP Alameda/San Francisco, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1969-1972 (Box 144, Folder 57)
    - San Francisco, PP Alameda/San Francisco, 1975-1978 (Box 144, Folder 58)
    - Oakland, PP Alameda/San Francisco, 1970-1974 (Box 144, Folder 59)
    - San Francisco
      - PP Alameda/San Francisco, Merger: PP League of Alameda County, Oakland, 1969-1970 (Box 144, Folder 60)
      - Affiliate, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1951-1970 (Box 144, Folder 61)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence, 1950-1970 (Box 144, Folder 62)
      - PP Association, 1968-1970 (Box 145, Folder 1)
      - PP Association, 1967 (Box 145, Folder 2)
      - PP Association, 1965-1966 (Box 145, Folder 3)
      - PP Association, 1964 (Box 145, Folder 4)
    - Oakland, PP Alameda/San Francisco, Reports, Clinics, 1973 (Box 145, Folder 5)
    - San Francisco, PP Association, Reports, Clinics, 1964-1967 (Box 145, Folder 6)
    - Oakland
      - PP Alameda/San Francisco, Publicity, 1970-1971 (Box 145, Folder 7)
      - PP Alameda/San Francisco, Reports, General, 1969-1973 (Box 145, Folder 8)
      - PP Alameda/San Francisco, Reports, Members from 1970
        - 1970-1973 (Box 145, Folder 9)
        - 1976-1978 (Box 145)
    - San Francisco
      - PP Association, Reports, Members, 1964-1971 (Box 145, Folder 10)
      - PP Association, Reports, General, 1963-1969 (Box 145, Folder 11)
      - Field Trips, 1953-1963 (Box 145, Folder 12)
      - PP Association, Publicity Pamphlets, etc., 1955-1970 (Box 145, Folder 13)
    - Los Angeles
      - Regional Family Planning Council, Inc. from 1969
        - 1969-1973 (Box 145, Folder 14)
        - 1975-1977 (Box 145)
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, from 1965
        - 1967-1974 (Box 145, Folder 15)
        - 1976-1977 (Box 145)
      - Affiliation, PPWP Los Angeles, Correspondence, 1976-1979 (Box 145, Folder 16)
      - Affiliation, PP Area Council, Correspondence from 1965
        - 1965-1974 (Box 145, Folder 17)
        - 1975 (Box 145)
      - PPWP Los Angeles, Legal, 1978-1979 (Box 145, Folder 18)
      - PPWP, 1970-1974 (Box 145, Folder 19)
      - PPWP Los Angeles, 1975-1979 (Box 145, Folder 20)
      - PP Area Council, 1964-1969 (Box 145, Folder 21-23)
      - PPWP/Los Angeles, "New Times Magazine" Charges, 1974 (Box 145, Folder 24)
      - PP Federation Council of Greater Los Angeles, Medical Advisory Committee, 1964-1965 (Box 145, Folder 25)
      - Reports, Clinics, 1977 (Box 145, Folder 26)
      - Greater Los Angeles PP, Reports, General, 1964-1969 (Box 145, Folder 27)
      - Greater Los Angeles PP, Reports, Members from 1964
        - 1964-1972 (Box 145, Folder 28)
        - 1976 (Box 145)
      - Greater Los Angeles PP, Publicity, 1964-1972 (Box 145, Folder 29)
      - A Proposal to Expand Family Planning in Los Angeles County, 1968 (Box 145, Folder 30)
      - Dr. Gordon Perkin's Trip, 12/6-11/64, 1964-1966 (Box 145, Folder 31)
      - Dick Mitchell, Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 145, Folder 32)
      - Still, Mrs. Peggie, Consultant, 1964-1966 (Box 145, Folder 33-34)
      - Still, Mrs. Peggie, Consultant, Reports, 1964-1965 (Box 145, Folder 35)
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1953-1964 (Box 146, Folder 1)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence, 1949-1969 (Box 146, Folder 2)
      - PP Center, 1960-1968 (Box 146, Folder 3-5)
      - Situation, Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 146, Folder 6)
      - Field Trips, 1953-1963 (Box 146, Folder 7)
      - PP, Reports, Clinics, 1964-1969 (Box 146, Folder 8)
      - PP Center, Reports, General, 1964-1966 (Box 146, Folder 9)
      - PP Centers, Reports, Members, 1960-1968 (Box 146, Folder 10)
      - Fund Raising Event, Fall 1962, 1961-1963 (Box 146, Folder 11)
      - Medical Workshops, 9/8/1962 (Box 146, Folder 12)
      - PP Center, Publicity, 1958-1980 (Box 146, Folder 13)
      - 1958-1967 (Box 146, Folder 14)
      - 1963-1969 (Box 146, Folder 15)
      - 1963-1965 (Box 146, Folder 16)
      - 1964 (Box 146, Folder 17)
      - 1964-1969 (Box 146, Folder 18)
      - 1967 (Box 146, Folder 19)
      - Council (New Affiliate), 1964-1966 (Box 146, Folder 20)
    - Wilmar (San Gabriel)
      - Field Trip, 1950 (Box 147, Folder 1)
      - Mothers' Conference Clinic, 1940-1951 (Box 147, Folder 2)
    - San Jose
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1965
        - 1964-1974 (Box 147, Folder 3)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 147)
      - Affiliation, PP Santa Clara County, Correspondence from 1964
        - 1964-1973 (Box 147, Folder 4)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 147)
      - Field Trips, 1960-1963 (Box 147, Folder 5)
      - PP Association of Santa Clara County from 1974
        - 1974 (Box 147, Folder 6)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 147)
      - PP Santa Clara County, 1965-1973 (Box 147, Folder 7)
      - Reports, General, 1965-1969 (Box 147, Folder 8)
      - Reports, Members from 1963
        - 1963-1970 (Box 147, Folder 9)
        - 1975-1977 (Box 147)
      - Publicity, 1965-1966 (Box 147, Folder 10)
    - San Mateo
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1966
        - 1966-1972 (Box 147, Folder 11)
        - 1978 (Box 147)
      - Affiliation, Correspondence from 1966
        - 1967-1972 (Box 147, Folder 12)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 147)
      - PP Association from 1966
        - 1965-1974 (Box 147, Folder 13)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 147)
      - Reports, Clinics, 1972 (Box 147, Folder 14)
      - Reports, General, 1966-1974 (Box 147, Folder 15)
      - Reports, Members from 1966
        - 1966-1972 (Box 147, Folder 16)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 147)
    - Marin County
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1950
        - 1950-1970 (Box 147, Folder 17)
        - 1976-1979 (Box 147)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1957
        - 1957-1974 (Box 147, Folder 18)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 147)
    - San Raphael, PP Association of Marin County from 1973
      - 1973-1974 (Box 147, Folder 19)
      - 1975-1979 (Box 147)
    - Marin County
      - PP Association, 1957-1972 (Box 147, Folder 20)
      - Field Trips, 1953-1963 (Box 147, Folder 21)
      - PP, Reports, General, 1963-1969 (Box 147, Folder 22)
      - PP, Reports, Members from 1960
        - 1960-1972 (Box 147, Folder 23)
        - 1976-1978 (Box 147)
      - PP, Publicity, 1963-1968, undated (Box 147, Folder 24)
    - Santa Ana/ Orange
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, Documents, 1980 (Box 147, Folder 25)
      - Affiliation, PP Association Orange County, Correspondence, 1979 (Box 147, Folder 26)
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1970
        - 1970-1974 (Box 147, Folder 27)
        - 1976 (Box 147)
      - Affiliation, PP Orange County, Correspondence from 1970
        - 1970-1974 (Box 147, Folder 28)
        - 1975-1977 (Box 147)
      - Affiliation, PP Orange County, Correspondence, 1965-1969 (Box 147, Folder 29)
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1965-1968 (Box 147, Folder 30)